ADISE MAMOYE

WEB DEVELOPER

- **5**16-838-9131
- adisemamo211@gmail.com
- Q Jacksonville, Florida
- https://www.adise-mamo.com

PROFILE

Passionate software developer specializing in frontend development using Vue.js with a comprehensive understanding of the entire web stack. Thrives when working on full-stack projects and constantly explores new technologies to learn, develop, and improve each day.

SKILLS

- Frontend: Vue.js, React.js,
 JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap,
 Material-UI, Vuetify
- Backend: Node.js, Express.js
- Database: PostgreSQL, Firestore (Firebase)
- Version Control: Git, GitHub,
 SourceTree
- Tools: Redux, Prisma, Firebase Auth, Firebase Hosting, Azure DevOps, CI CD

EDUCATION

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Developers Institute TLV 03/2022 - 06/2022

LANGUAGES

English, Hebrew, Amharic

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Wyze - Cloud Knowledge Management System 01/2023 - Present

- Lead the frontend development of a cloud-based knowledge management system
- Reduced support team response time by 42%, improving overall customer satisfaction.
- Implemented CI/CD pipeline that decreased deployment time by 70%
- Led the migration from Vue 2 to Vue 3 for the major project.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Moyae - Electronic Health Record System 07/2022 - 01/2023

- Optimized treatment time for ophthalmologists and optometrists by developing a comprehensive Electronic Health Record (EHR) system that improved operational efficiency.
- Played a key role in developing scalable, maintainable code for various system features
- Integrated advanced frontend technologies to provide a modern user interface
- Supported long-term application growth and reliability.